(Penny:)Is that crazy?
(Leonard:)Yes.
No, it's not crazy. It's a...
(Leonard:)It's a paradox.
(Leonard:)Paradoxes are part of nature.
I mean, think about light.
(Leonard:)If you look at Huygens, light is a wave,
as confirmed by the double-slit experiments.
(Leonard:)But then, along comes Albert Einstein...
(Leonard:)...and discovers that light
behaves like particles too.
(Leonard:)Well, I didn't make it worse.
(Penny:)Oh, I'm so sorry I'm such a mess.
(Penny:)And on top of everything else,
I'm all gross from moving...
...and my stupid shower doesn't work.
(Leonard:)Our shower works.
(Penny:)Really? Would it be totally weird
if I used it?
(Sheldon:)- Yes.
- No.
- No?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Leonard:)It's right down the hall.
(Penny:)Okay, thanks.
(Penny:)You guys are really sweet.
(Sheldon:)Well, this is an interesting development.